我第一次碰这把刀的时候
First time I touched that blade.
我就知道没人能阻止我
I knew that I wouldn't be stopped.
我一定会杀了Abaddon
And that I would take down Abaddon.
或者其它我必须干掉的东西
And anything else that I had to.
我很高兴这把初刃给了你力量
I'm glad the blade gives you strength.
冷静 还是什么的
The calm or whatever.
但我开始觉得
I gotta say I'm starting to think.
这把刀还有其他作用
The blade is doing something else, too.
这场天使之间的战争无可避免了 是吧
So this war between angels is really gonna happen.
可以避免 如果我能找出合适的外交策略
Not if I can find a diplomatic option.
我知道你真的相信这是为了大局着想
I know you truly believe is for the grader good.
你对Metatron的误信 会让你再次失望
Your mistaken trust in Metatron will bring you down again.
大门都被封印了 谁都进不去
The gates are sealed, no one can get in.
谁跟你说大门了
Who said anything about gates.
有秘密入口还要大门干吗
You don't need gates when you have a private portal.
不会有这种东西存在的
You can't have something like that.
可以有 如果那个传送门到处移动
You can if it moves around from place to place.
头儿想把它放哪儿就能放哪儿
If it's wherever the boss wants it to be.
你体内偷来的荣光还还好使吗
How's that stolen grace inside you working out.
很好
Fine.
不 不好
No, it's not.
Dean
Dean.
我认识你吗
Do I know you.
我们是老相识了
We go way back.
Tessa
Tessa.
我知道他们不知道的事
I know something they don't know.
结局
The ending.
我怎样能成功不重要
How I get there doesn't matter.
只要每个人都做好自己的工作
As long as everybody plays their part.
我要一个脱脂非乳制香草味冰淇林球
Yeah, give me one scoop of the no fat non-dairy vanilla.
要四分之一勺无糖的焦糖 和十个
With a quarter teaspoon of the sugar-free caramel and ten.
不是九个 不是十一个
Not nine, not eleven.
蓝莓
Blueberries.
记住了吗
Got it.
很好
Good.
你想吃什么 亲爱的
What do you want, honey.
那个
That.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我知道这不关我的事
I know this is none of my business.
的确不关你的事 走开
You're right it's not, go away.
你父母在哪
Where are your parents.
我没父母
I don't have parents.
我是天使
I'm an angel.
是啊 你是个小天使
Yeah, you're a little angel.
你坐这儿你妈妈知道吗
Did your mother know you're sitting here.
快吃成糖尿病了
Eating diabetes.
快跑
You need to run.
什么
What.
快跑
Now.
反应不错
Nice reflexes.
发型更炫酷
Better hair.
你什么情况
What's wrong with you.
我差点开枪打到你
I could've shot you.
你怎么不睡觉 我们两小时前才躺下
Why aren't you sleeping, we got in like two hours ago.
不累 而且我们有活干
No tired, and we got work to do.
穿上你的舞鞋 王子叫你去舞会呢
Put on your dance shoes and let's boogie.
好吧 什么事
All right, what's up.
我给Cass打了电话
I called Cass.
他说密苏里州出了点问题
He said something's going down in Missouri.
什么问题
What kind of something.
他说在电话上不方便说
He said he couldn't talk about it on the phone.
为什么
Why.
因为他是个怪人
Because he is a weird guy.
因为他又怪又蠢
OK?He's a weird dorky little guy.
但他刚好手下有一个天使军团 哥们儿
But, he happens to have an army of angels behind him, man.
不得不说
Even though we have to say.
如果我们想杀Metatron
That if we're gonna take a shot at Metatron.
他的军队可能会有用
It might be useful.
怎么 你觉得我们需要初刃
What, do you think we need the first blade.
为什么不留在这儿呢
Why we just, leave that here.
我们谈过了 我们决定
We talked about this, and we decided that.
不 这样说不公平
No, no fairness.
不是我们决定的 是你
We didn't decide, you did.
好吧 我决定的
Ok I decided.
那个可以杀死任何东西的棍子
That hockey stick that can kill anything.
用起来会很顺手
Might come in handy.
你能把我怎样
So sue me.
这件事我们讨论过多少次了
How many times have we been around this block.
使用这么强大的魔法一定是要付出代价的
Magic that powerful comes at a price.
现在我们不知道这个代价是什么
And right now we don't know what that price is.
我很好 我简直棒呆了
I'm fine, I'm fanfriggingtastic.
我很高兴 真的
I'm glad, honestly.
我没说我们得把它埋了
I'm not saying that we bury that thing.
我是说等到真正用的时候再拿出来
I'm saying we just save it for when we really need it.
对付Crowley，对付Metatron
Crowley, Metatron.
Boss大战
The big boss fights.
你不用一直带着它不是吗
You don't have to have it with you all the time, right.
把它留下吧
I mean just leave it.
拜托了
Please.
没问题
No problem.
谢谢
Thank you.
Spears和Aguilera探长 联邦调查局的
Agent Spears and Aguilera, FBI.
是的
Uh huh.
你们的同事说你们会来
Your partner said you'll be along.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你们赶来
Thank you for coming.
Spears和Aguilera是吗
Spears and Aguilera.
我发现你们的化名
I realized that your alias.
通常都是流行音乐家的名字
Are usually the names of popular musicians.
过来 看看这个
Come here, take a look at this.
看 另外的尸体也是一样的
Look, the other bodies are the same.
烧焦的躯壳
Burnt out husks.
这到底是什么 大规模屠杀吗
OK so what is this, some sort of mass smiting.
我也不知道这是什么
I don't know what this was.
从来没见过
Never seen anything like it.
死了六个人
Six humans died here.
一个天使
And one angel.
你手下的吗
One of yours.
他曾是个好战士
Was a good soldier.
这次攻击
This attack.
我知道他想挑起战争
I knew he wanted a war.
就算是他也不该做出这么卑鄙的事
But this, this is abhorrent even for him.
等一下
Just a second.
我等了你一下
I gave you a second.
有时你还真是个典型的天使
You are such an angel sometimes.
你想干什么
What do you want.
谈谈今晚的事
To talk about tonight.
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
不我们 我们正在失势 Metatron
No, we, we're losing, Metatron.
跟随Castiel的人比我们多
Castiel's followers outnumber us.
尽管他们还没闯进我们的领地
And while they haven't gone on our fence.
但他们证明了自己有这个能力
They have proven capable.
他们成功阻止了你杀死他
They have stopped you from killing him.
还有我
And me for example.
我说过了那次暗杀计划是个契机
I told you we had our shot with operation Lee Harvey.
我们也把握住了
And we took it.
我下达命令
I gave the orders.
没人会伤害你
You weren't to be harmed.
你让他们跟踪我
You have me followed.
还没说你跑去偷会敌人这事呢
And you met with the enemy.
偷偷摸摸的
In secret.
那句关于石头和罪恶的老话是怎么说的
What is that old line about sins and stones.
他说了
He spoke.
我误信了他的谎话
He lied and I listened.
就是这样
That's it.
但我是为天堂效劳
But I serve heaven.
我为你效力
I serve you.
很好
Good.
别忘了这一点
Don't forget it.
我也搞不懂这股全民Cass热是怎么回事
I don't get this whole Cass love fest, either.
我给天使们指引回家的路
I'm offering our people a way home.
但他们还是选择他不选我
And still, still, they're choosing him over me.
我是说 当然 他是很帅
I mean sure he's cute.
Castiel有一种独特的 魅力
And Castiel has this simple charm.
就像一个智力低下的小狗
It's like a mentally deficient puppy.
但我也很迷人啊
But I'm lovable.
还很幽默
I'm funny.
我还让上帝笑了
I made God laugh.
两次
Twice.
是你要他带领军队的
You are the one who asked him to lead an army.
但我也没想到他擅长这个
And I didn't think he would be good at it.
你今晚要和Tyrus见面
You are meeting tonight…Tyrus.
剩余的天使军团
He controls the largest.
几乎都掌握在他手里
Independent faction of angels left.
我必须要给他留个好印象
And I have to make a good impression.
我知道
I know.
我有计划
I gotta a plan.
不是我想的那样吧
It's not that, is it.
闭嘴
Shut up.
长官
Commander.
这个场景好诡异
Oh this just creepy.
Sam Dean
Sam Dean.
这是Hannah
This is Hannah.
Winchester兄弟
Winchesters.
久闻大名
I heard so much about you.
这多亏了Cass 他是我们的粉丝
What can I say, Cass is a fan.
我马上开示检查这些证据
I'll start to examine the evidence.
长官 今早Josiah点名时不在
Sir, this morning Josiah wasn't at roll call.
点名
Uh roll call.
你们还要点名
You hold a roll call.
他们喜欢听我念他们的名字
They like to hear me say their names.
我知道有的女人就喜欢这样
I know a couple of women like that.
Ezra被杀后就没人见过Josiah了
No one's seen Josiah since Ezra was murdered.
你们认为是Josiah杀的
You think Josiah is the killer.
间谍就是他
And he is a mole.
还能是谁
Well who else.
我们到处找过了 但他消失了
We search the grounds but he vanished.
他没有翅膀是办不到的
Not without wings.
没错他是天使 但现在也只能用人类的方式
He's an angel but he still travels like a human.
这就意味着他只能走路开车
Which means walk, drive.
肯定有迹可循
Means he's gonna leave a trail.
好吧
Alright.
他的皮囊叫什么
What was the vessel's name.
Sean Flynn 奥马哈人
Sean Flynn from Omaha.
好
Okay.
是这个人吗
Is this the guy.
就是他
Yeah that's him.
很好
Alright.
看起来他刚刚在科罗拉多
Looks like someone just used his credit card.
用信用卡在加油站加了油
At a Gas-n-Sip in Colorado.
专业领域就是这样操作的
That's how we do things in the pros.
长官
Commander.
我发现了些事
I have something.
这只手机里存了一段录像
This phone's memory chip has a video time-stamped.
就在爆炸前拍的
Just before explosion.
万众期待的时刻到来了
And now the moment you've all been waiting for.
不
No.
为了Castiel
I do this for Castiel.
这到底是什么玩意
What the hell was that.
我不知道
I don't know.
我绝不会指使天使
I didn't I would never ask an angel.
让他们用自杀的方式滥杀无辜
To sacrifice himself to kill innocents.
太恶心了
I'm gonna be sick.
为什么这个天使在冰激凌店自爆
Why would an angel blow up.
同时喊了你的大名
A Colonel Scoop's in your name.
这不是他的重点
That's not what he was doing.
倒回去
Roll it back.
看 那是个天使 她叫Esther
There, that was an angel, Esther.
她是Metaron的手下
She's one of Metatron's.
所以 这是买凶杀人
So this is some kind of hit.
我不知道
I don't know.
别再说你不知道了
Stop saying you don't know.
你不可以相信我会做这样的事
You can't think I would allow some things like this.
我知道你想当个好人
I know you try to be a good guy, okay.
我懂 你努力了
I do.You try.
但你领导的这他妈是个邪教
But what you got here this is a freaking cult.
Dean
Dean.
上次你得势的时候
Last time you had this kind of juice.
你对人类和天使大开杀戒
You did kill humans and angels and you did nothing.
什么正事儿都没干 还骗的我和Sam团团转
But lie to me and Sam about it the whole damn time.
我们能
Can we, uh.
我们能去别的地儿谈这事儿吗 伙计们
Can we take this somewhere else, guys.
你能别这么激动吗 Dean
Will you stow the baggage, Dean.
听着 我们手头有一个案子
Look, we've got a case.
我们要工作
Let's work it.
Cass 你认识录像里那个天使吗
Cass, did you know the angel in that video.
认识 他叫Orin
Yes, his name was Oren.
他是个新来的
He was a new recruit.
在社区外围帮工
He worked in community outreach.
什么意思
And what does that mean.
我的一些追随者进驻了社区医院
Some of my troops are stationed at a local hospital.
能帮多少帮多少
They help where they can.
一些小的医学奇迹 惹不起多大风浪
Minor miracles, it's nothing that would draw attention.
那他为什么会出现在那个录像里
So, what was he doing in that video.
给了自己一刀
With the stabbing.
他胸上刻的天使语记号
The Enochian runes that were carved in his chest.
应该是用来聚集荣光的
I…I think that they were meant to focus energy.
当他捅了自己一刀 瞬间释放了能量
When he stabbed himself, it unleashed all that power.
那个女孩呢
So, what about the girl.
她怎么了
What happened to her.
如果她是目标的话 荣光的爆发就指向她
If she was a target, then the blast was focused on her.
这样的话 她只能是被分解了
Then more likely than not, she, she was atomized.
那我们现在怎么办
So, what do we do now.
你什么都不用做
Well, you don't do jack.
我和Sam去一趟医院
Me and Sam will head to the hospital.
看能不能找到
See if we can find somebody.
知道这些移动核弹的人
Who knew this…walking nuke.
等等 他们是我的人 我能帮上忙
Hold on, these are my poeple, I can help.
这正是问题所在
Well, that's sort of the problem.
只要Charlie一出现
I mean, the Manson girls aren't gonna give us.
Manson就什么都不会说
A straight answer with Charlie in the room.
所以 你也一样不用管
So just hang back.
那我就只能干等了吗
So I should just sit here.
差不多
Pretty much.
不
No.
如果你不让我帮忙
If you don't want my help.
我就去科罗拉多找Josiah
Then I will follow Josiah's trail to Colorado.
我必须得做点儿什么 Dean
I have to do something, Dean.
好吧
All right, fine.
但是Sam要跟着你
But Sam's coming with you.
- 什么 - 你不相信我了吗
- What?-Because you don't trust me.
他去帮你
To help.
Abaddon死了
Abaddon is dead.
死了一个 站起来一片
And then some.
哦 不
Oh, no.
好吧
Okay.
如此不详
Ominous.
Dean最近是不是有点儿不对劲
Does Dean seem different to you.
是啊
Yeah.
最近 他就像通了电门一样
Lately, he seems to be amped up.
很烦躁
You know, on edge.
该隐之印的影响
The effects of the mark.
还能因为什么
Or what else.
他的确看起来很生气
He does seem angry.
我是说 他总是有点暴躁
I mean, he's always a little angry.
但是现在更严重
But now it seems like…more.
有一部分的他真的觉得
A part of him actually believes that.
是我让那些天使
I ordered those angles to…you know.
Sam 你不这样觉得吧
Sam, you don't.Do you.
不 Cass 听我说
No, man.Cass, listen.
有奇怪的事情正在发生
We got weird thing going on back there.
那些天使 他们盯着你的样子
Those are the angles, the way they stare at you.
就像盯着什么摇滚明星 或者宗教大能
It's like you, part rock star, part L.Ron.
他们信仰我
They put their faith in me.
这可能就是问题所在
And maybe that's the problem.
人们一直都在做一些混账的事
I mean, people have been doing messed-up crap.
以信仰的名义 以上帝的名义
In name of faith, in name of the God.
从古至今
Since forever.
我不是试图扮演上帝
Not trying to play God.
只是想把我的族人送回家
Just trying to get my people home.
好球 太棒了
Yes, well done.
这是个简单的游戏
It's such a simple game.
你们一定会爱上球撞柱的声音
And boy, you gotta love the sound of those pins, huh.
漂亮极了 木头的交响曲
Beautiful, a symphony of wood.
你应该听说了我们的提议
So, you've heard our offer.
听说了 我在协议上签字
Yeah, I signed on the dotted line.
我手下所有人 都能回天堂
All my people, they get a ticket upstairs.
如果我们不想去呢
What if we don't wanna go.
可是那里是家
But it's home.
但那儿很无聊
It's boring.
天堂没有保龄球这种东西
There's nothing like this in heaven.
我可以给你建一个保龄球馆
I could whip you off a bowling alley.
但是 那也不一样
But, it wouldn't…
闻闻这儿的味道
I mean just smell that.
旧鞋子和酒精
Old shoes and alcoholism.
权威
Authenticity.
你就因为打保龄球反抗我吗
So wait, you are turning me down because of bowling.
我也喜欢一个人做事
And I like being an independent operator.
我听说你快输了
And I hear you are losing.
而且我讨厌你的长相
And I hate your face.
我可以换张新脸
Well, I can get a new face.
换了脸你也还是你 一个书呆子
You will still be you, a nerd.
想要跻身明星学生的行列
Trying to be one of the popular kids.
好吧 该来点真格的了
OK, time for he hard sell.
算了吧 你用刀刺我
Please, you knife me.
我的人就会全跑到Castiel那边
And all my guys will go running to Castiel.
即使是你 也不会干那么傻的事儿
Even you are not that stupid.
不过嘛
I'll tell you what.
你要是赢了我 我们就有得聊
You out-bowl me, we'll walk.
我见过他 警官
Yeah I saw him, officer.
给一辆木纹小客车加了油
Filled up some old…woody station wagon.
想必你没记下他的车牌号
Don't suppose you got the license plate number.
哈哈 没
Haha no.
他好像要去蒙大拿州的普雷
He was heading to an address at Pray Montana.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that.
他问我怎么去来着
The guy asked for directions.
你要我写下来吗
You want me to write that down.
对
Yes.
现在就写 谢谢
Now, please.
我怎么称呼你
What do I call you.
我的天使名有十八个音节那么长
My angelic name is eighteen syllables long.
所以你还是叫我明星员工吧
Let's stick with Flagstaff.
明白
Copy.
所以你认识这个叫Oren的家伙
So you knew this Oren guy.
我们一起在医院工作
We worked together at the hospital.
他是个开心果 人又聪明
He was a joy, bright.
充满活力
Full of life.
没错 他还有爆炸性的性格
Yeah, he had a real explosive personality.
你以为这是个玩笑吗
Do you think this is a joke.
你看到我笑了吗
Do you see me laughing.
关于他你还知道些什么
Is there anything else you can tell me about him.
比如 为什么他把自己点了
For example, why he lighted his own fuse.
无可奉告 我可以走了吗
No, can I go.
有人等着我救命呢
I have lives to save.
彼此彼此
Welcome to club.
笑什么
Somethin' funny.
一点也不好笑 哈哈
Not funny, haha.
只是 你觉得自己在帮助别人
But you, thinking you help people.
这一点很好笑
It's amusing.
我在帮助别人
I help people.
动脉阻塞 肿瘤等等
Clogged artery here, tumor there.
我日行一善 你呢
I do good in this world, you.
你只相信枪能解决所有问题
You believe every problem can be solved with a gun.
你想当英雄 可皮囊下面
You played the hero but underneath the hype.
你就是个杀人犯
You are a killer.
手上沾满了鲜血
With ocean's of blood on his hands.
我恨像你这样的人
I hate man like you.
甜心 再没有第二个像我这样的人了
Honey, there ain't no other men like me.
别 求你了
Don't, please.
Oren 他的同党
Oren, friends.
Constantine和Tessa
Constantine and Tessa.
Tessa 死神Tessa
Tessa, the Reaper Tessa.
你认识她
You know her.
（普雷 蒙大拿州）
加油站里那人说的就是这辆车吧 对吧
That looks like the car the guy in gas station talking about, right.
说不定Josiah还在附近
Maybe Josiah is still around.
Sam 这地方散发着强大的能量
Sam, this place's radiating power.
我很久都没遇见过这种情况了
I never felt anything like this since.
自从天堂沦陷
Since heaven.
我们必须进去
We have to get in here.
行了
Alright.
让我来
Step aside.
我来搞定
I got this.
我搞不定
I don't got this.
晚上好 Tessa
Howdy Tessa.
你今晚不是应该在医院值班吗
You are supposed to be working at the hospital tonight.
我去找过你 你不在
But when I stopped by, you were gone.
救护车也不在
So was the ambulance.
听听行家的意见吧
Pro tips.
医院的车都装了GPS
They all have GPS.
多谢告知
Good to know.
你怎么来了
So you are here, why.
不会是歌舞剧爱好者吧
Just love musical theatre.
我只喜欢Fiddler
Only if it's Fiddler.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
不行
We can't.
我有个约会
Sorta got a date.
你去不了了
Not happening.
另一个在哪儿
Where's the other one.
Constantine在哪儿
Where's Constantine.
- 祝你下次好运 - 谢谢
- Better luck next time - Thanks.
Metatron
Metatron.
为了Castiel
I do this for Castiel.
我检查了所有门窗
I checked all those windows and doors.
什么都没有
No luck.
你呢
What about you.
有收获吗
You find anything.
有
I think so.
天使语
It's Enochian.
类似谜语的东西
I believe it's some sort of riddle.
为什么六害怕七
Why is six afraid of seven.
难道是因为七是素数
I assume it's because seven is a prim number.
你知道素数总是让人心生敬畏
And prim numbers can be intimidating.
是因为七吃了九
It's because seven eight nine.
文字游戏
Word play.
答案就是钥匙
The answer is the key.
就像指环王里的都灵之门
Like the Doors of Durin in the Lord of the Rings.
等一下
Wait a second.
你知道指环王
You know about the Lord of the Rings.
我现在可是流行文化大手
I'm very pop culture savvy now.
嗨 他怎么样了
Hey, how is he.
他是Cass
He's Cass.
你呢 你怎么样了
What about you, how's it going.
我很好 出了趟门 呼吸了新鲜空气
Great.Went out.Got some air.
还碰到了一个老朋友
Met an old friend.
跟Sam打个招呼 Tessa
Say hi to Sam.Tessa.
你哥哥是个神经病 Sam
Your brother's a psycho, Sam.
住嘴
Stop.
发生什么事了
What's going on.
你先说
You first.
我知道他是总指挥官的朋友
I know he's the commander's friend.
我知道我们应该装作很喜欢他的样子
And I know we are supposed to pretend that we like him.
但是那个猴子居然拿刀抵着我的脖子
But that ape put a knife to my throat.
Tessa
Tessa.
你干什么
What are you doing.
你来告诉她吧
You want to tell her.
哦 上帝啊
Oh God.
没有上帝
There is no God.
只有Castiel
It's only Castiel.
好吧 聊天结束
Oh, and you're done.
你伤了她
You wounded her.
应该说我刚拆除了炸弹
Well, I defused.
划掉她刻在身上的那个
Cut up that Old Testament graffiti.
圣经旧约图案
She carved into herself.
我觉得那应该能解除咒语
I figured that would break the spell.
现在 你要拿她怎么办
Now, what will you do to her.
猜
Guess.
折磨她
Torture.
没创意
Predictable.
我们得确定还有没有其它的自爆者
We need to know if there's other bombers out there.
不 我不同意
No, I won't allow it.
我知道Tessa的计划
I know what Tessa was planning.
的确很恐怖
It was horrible.
但是只有一个人能惩罚她
But there's only one person who can punish her.
让我猜猜 这么高
Let me guess.This big.
穿着风衣 休闲鞋
Trench coat, sensible shoes.
你必须理解
You have to understand that.
Castiel是唯一能把我们团结在一起的人
Castiel is the only thing holding us together.
一个月前 这里一半的天使
A month ago, half the angels in this place.
还在想着除掉另一半的天使
Were trying to kill the other half.
Castiel让我们有了追求
Castiel has given us a purpose.
但更重要的是
But more than that.
他教会我们怎样和平共处
He's given us a way to live in peace.
我们有规则 秩序
We have rules, order.
如果你擅自做出决定
If I let you take matters into your own hands.
那他们是不是也可以这么不守规矩
What's to stop one of them from doing the same.
你可以和她先谈谈
You can talk to her.
你也应该和她谈谈
You should talk to her.
但是别带刀进去
But leave the blade outside.
你们是在请求还是命令
Are you asking or telling.
这不是请求
We are not asking.
你确定你不想调头回去吗 Cass
You sure you don't want to go back, Cass.
听着 如果Tessa真是Dean说的那样
Look, if Dean's right about Tessa.
不 我想 只是
No, I do.I just.
给我点儿时间
Give me a second.
只有忏悔者可通过
Only the penitent man shall pass.
Cass 等等
Cass, wait.
圣战奇兵 好吧
The last crusade, OK.
好的 我们从简单的问题开始
Well, let's start with an easy one.
你在为谁工作
Who are you working for.
Castiel
Castiel.
骗子
Liar.
你们这样的人 也许永远不会明白
People like you may never understand.
牺牲是必须的
Sacrifices have to be made.
你们在追杀坏人的时候
So you go after one of the bad guys.
如果几个人类爆炸了
And if a few humans get microwaved.
也没什么关系 是吗
No big deal, right.
在大计划中
In the grand scheme.
他们无关紧要
They don't matter.
Tessa 你大错特错了
Oh, Tessa, you're so wrong.
当Castiel来找我的时候
When Castiel came to me.
他交待了我的使命
He told me what I had to do.
他说我被选中的原因是我很坚强
He said I was chosen because I was strong.
其他的人 无法应付这些事
Others, they couldn't handle this.
他们都太软弱
They are too weak.
冷静点
Settle down.
你觉得她说的是实话吗
Do you think she's telling the truth.
她认为她说的是实话
She thinks she is.
Sam 我们找到了
Sam, we found it.
什么
What.
通向天堂的门
It's the door to heaven.
真的吗
Seriously.
还有什么
What else.
能让Metatron这样千方百计避人耳目
Would Metatron go to such great length to protect.
我能听见
I can hear it.
它对我的呼唤 Sam
It's calling me, Sam.
如果我们控制了这扇门
If we control this door.
我们就能向Metatron宣战
We can take the fight to Metatron.
也许我们都用不着打仗了
We might not even need the fight at all.
Cass 等一下
Cass, wait.
什么情况
The hell.
欢迎来到你的私人天堂 Castiel
Welcome to your personal heaven, Castiel.
祝你能找到真的天堂
Good luck finding the real one.
什么
What.
什么意思
Why.
是Josiah 他身上有圣油的味道
It's Josiah, he reeks of holy oil.
是啊
Yeah.
看起来他一个人偷溜回家了
Looks like he got Home Alone-ed.
这么说 一切都是个谎言
So all this, it's a lie.
本应在这里的 传送门
Supposed to be here…gate.
他告诉我 在Ezra的事之后 他告诉我
He told me, after Ezra, he told me.
说我应该追随他
That I should come to him.
Metatron告诉我 我能回家
Metatron told me that I could go home.
我只是想回家而已
I just want to go home.
- 来 让我 - 不
- Here, let me - No.
与其被你救活
I would rather die.
我还不如这样死去 Castiel
Than owe my life to you Castiel.
你总是那么的高尚
You play at being noble.
看起来跟我们一样
Play at you being one of us.
但当我看着你的眼睛
But I look into your eyes.
回望着我的不是一个天使
I don't see an angel staring back at me.
你的朋友呢
Where's your friend.
现在只有你和我了
Just you and me now.
谈谈我们两个吧 毕竟我们还有过一段历史呢
Let's talk about us, I mean we've got history, yeah.
是啊
Sure.
我记得我们美好的邂逅
I still remember our meet-cute.
当时你快死了
You're dying.
美好时光啊
Good times.
听着
Here's a deal.
我喜欢你 Tess 你要明白
I like you, Tess, okay, for an angel.
但是你到底为什么会参与进来
But tell me why you are doing this.
Castiel
Castiel.
别管什么Cass 你为什么这么做
Forget Cass, why are you doing this.
你究竟为什么舍得放弃自己的生命
What would make a person wanna pop their top, huh.
我也有过不好的时候
I mean, look I have been in a bad shape.
但是我从来没堕落至此
But I have never been that damn low.
大概是我忍受不了那些哀嚎了吧
I guess I just can't take the screaming.
谁的哀嚎
Who's screaming.
所有人的
All of them.
那些走失的灵魂
The lost souls.
本来可以安眠于
That ones can't get into heaven.
天堂的灵魂
Now that it's been boarded up.
我能听到他们
I hear them.
他们是那么的困惑
They are so confused.
如此的痛苦
They are in so much pain.
我想做的只不过是帮帮他们
All I wanna do is help them.
这是我的工作 我的职责
It's what I do, it's my job.
但我现在无能为力
But I can't.
所以我受尽折磨
So I suffered.
直到死亡 归为虚无
Until death, nothingness.
突然间 死亡也不是那么糟了
Suddenly it didn't seem so bad.
看起来很平静
It seemed quiet.
那你为什么不直接
So why don't you just jam an angel blade.
用匕首了断自己
In your throat and call it a day.
我想过
I thought about it.
但是我太弱了
But I was too weak.
直到Castiel给了我一个可以去死的理由
Till Castiel gave me a reason to die.
是啊
Yeah.
听起来不是我认识的那个Cass
He doesn't sound like the Cass I know.
但是他就是 不是吗
But doesn't it though.
你认识的那个Cass
And the Cass you know.
会瞒着你私自组建一个天使大军吗
Would he raise an army of angels without telling you.
这个Cass这么做了
Cause this Cass did.
我来告诉你个秘密吧
I'll tell you a secret.
外面还有更多人
There's more out there.
像我一样的人
Like me.
数不胜数
So many more.
你有名字吗
You got names.
剧透可不好哦
That would ruin all the fun.
不
No.
No.See.
好戏才刚刚开始
Fun just getting started.
Dean 你做了什么
Dean, what have you done.
我必须做的
What I had to.
彼此彼此
Welcome to the club.
谢谢
Thank you.
他抵抗了很久
He put up a fight.
出去
Get out.
你们真该瞧瞧被我打趴下的那10个人
You should have seen the other 10 guys.
他们说你杀了Tessa
They said you killed Tessa.
不算是 她自己捅了自己一刀
Not so much, she knifed herself.
是吗 那她为什么要自杀 Dean
Yeah?Why would she do that, Dean.
我也不知道 Sam
I don't know, Sam.
她当时一直在胡言乱语
She was saying all kinds of crap.
所以你就把初刃拿出来了是吗
So that's why you brought up the first blade.
他们告诉你了对吧
They told you about that.
我们说好了的
We had a deal.
我知道 但那个约定蠢透了
Well.It was a stupid deal.
是吗
Really.
如果你遵守约定 Tessa就不会死了
Cause if you stuck to it, Tessa will still be alive.
没有她 我们就什么胜算也没有
Without her, we ain't get jack.
你以为我不知道这些吗
You think I don't know that.
你以为我愿意看到这些事情发生吗
You think I wanted that happen.
我不知道 Dean 你愿意吗
I don't know, Dean, did you.
好了 够了 都停下
Alright, that's enough, stop it.
长官 抱歉 但是
Commander, I'm sorry, but.
有电话找你
You have a call.
Metatron打来的
From Metatron.
Castiel
Castiel.
见到我你一定不太开心吧
Bet you not happy to see me.
有人见到你会开心吗
Is anyone, ever.
Dean 你这点滑头都是从80年代
Dean, always with the.
B级动作片里学来的吧
B-grade '80s-action-movie wit.
你想干什么 Metatron
What do you want, Metatron.
只是通知混蛋Castiel一声 我还活着
Just to tell Asstiel there that I'm still alive.
他送来的那个自爆者 任务失败了
His bomber, failed.
什么自爆者
My bomber.
就是那个疯狂的家伙 拿着长刀 嘭地一声
The crazy guy, big knife, caploo-y.
我活地好好的 多谢关心
I'm fine, thanks for asking.
但是Gadreel受伤了
But Gadreel is wounded.
还有Tyrus
And Tyrus.
永远安息了
R.I.P.
还有 他那些追随者可不是你的死忠粉丝
His followers are not your biggest fans, by the way.
他们都转投于我了
They've all come over to my team.
我没有派任何人去杀你
I didn't send anyone to kill you.
拜托 别骗人了 Castiel
Oh, stop lying, Castiel.
你也敢跟我提骗人两个字
Who are you to lecture me on lying.
你的诡计多端 导致了天使们的坠落
Your deception, let to the fall.
我只是做了我该做的事
I did what I had to do.
我一直在做我必须做的
I always done what I have to do.
为了上帝 还有天使们
For God, and for the angels.
那当然 你是长着大胡子的修女特蕾莎
Sure, your mother Teresa with neck beard.
我的所作所为不能用好坏来衡量
What I did was neither good or bad.
我做的都是必须做的事
It was necessary.
一点小挫折会让我们更加强大
A small hardship to make us all stronger.
也会让我们重新团结起来
To make us a family again.
除了你让Gadreel杀掉的那些天使之外
Except for the angels you had Gadreel killed.
好吧 好吧
Okay, yes.
我一开始可能是有点过于激动了
Maybe I got a little carried away, at first.
但是如今不会再这样
But those days are over.
濒死体验会让你有全新的价值观
And near death experience makes you reevaluate.
所以仅此一次
So one time only.
我发出特赦令
I'm offering amnesty.
所有天使 无论曾犯下什么罪孽
Every angel, no matter what their sin.
都可以投靠我 然后回到天堂
May join me and return to heaven.
我会成为他们的上帝
I will be their God.
他们是我的天堂的新主人
And they will be my heavenly host.
我们为什么要跟随你
Why would we follow you.
看看周围吧 你们都见识过地球了
Look around, you've seen earth.
也都尝过了自由的滋味
You had a taste of free will.
我得问问 你真的喜欢自由吗
I gotta ask you, do you like it.
你们成群结队的跟随Castiel
The way you flocked off to follow Castiel tells me.
说明你们需要一个首领
You need to follow someone.
这是根植在你们基因中的
It's in your DNA.
但是Cass 他并不像你们想象中的那样
But Cass, he is not what you think he is.
他让天使们白白送死
He sends angels out to die.
你告诉他们关于
Have you told them.
你偷来的荣光了吗 Castiel
About your stolen grace, Castiel.
你的荣光是如何正在消逝
How it's fading away.
还有当它消耗殆尽 你也会一同毁灭
And when it burns out so are you.
看来没有了
So, no then.
我不是最完美的 但我是你们的最佳人选
I'm not the best, but I'm the best you've got.
你们想要留在Castiel身边 可以
You wanna stay with Castiel, fine.
但是他不过是在玩弄你们
But he is playing you.
因为一旦末日来临
Because in the end of the day.
他唯一在意的
The only thing he cares about.
只有他自己和那边的男孩二人组
Is himself and the Hardy Boys there.
该你们做出抉择了
You've got a choice to make.
明智点
Make the right one.
他在撒谎
He is lying.
荣光是怎么回事
About the grace.
一言难尽
It's complicated.
所以他说的是真的
So he wasn't lying.
除了荣光他说的都是假的
He was about everything else.
你相信我 对吗
You believe me, don't you.
我想要相信你 但是
I want to believe you, but I.
证明给我们看
We need proof.
说吧
Name it.
惩罚他
Punish him.
什么
What.
他杀了Tessa 破了我们的规矩
He murdered Tessa, he broke our rules.
你们都可以去死了
You all can go to hell.
Dean
Dean.
等等
Wait a second.
你给我们命令 Castiel
You give us order, Castiel.
而我们也将信任交予你
And we gave you our trust.
不要因为一个人而不顾大局
Don't lose it over one man.
这就是正义
This is justice.
不 我不能
No, I can't.
再见 Castiel
Goodbye, Castiel.
你说的没错
You're right.
只有我们才是正道
There's no other side.
欢迎加入
Welcome aboard.
Castiel的第一批追随者前来报道了
The first of Castiel's flock has come around.
剩下的人也会随之而来的
The rest will follow.
你应该告诉我 那个特别小组是干什么的
You should've told me what our…elite unit was for.
为什么 这又不关你的事
Why, it was none of your business.
Tessa
Tessa.
Constantine
Constantine.
是我召集了他们 而你
I recruited them and you.
你用花言巧语引诱他们去自毁
You brainwashed them into blowing themselves up.
所以呢
So.
这都是编剧的小伎俩
Well that's an old writer's trick.
制造点儿小起伏什么的
Flipping the script.
首先 你要制造一个坚不可摧的敌人形象
You start by building a seemingly unbeatable enemy.
比如说 死星
Like the Death Star.
或者
Or.
一个敌对天使 掌握着一个军队
A rival angel with a bigger…army.
这样的话 我看起来就略弱一筹
That way I look like the underdog.
但是紧接着
But then.
哦 不
Oh, no.
竞争目的变得不那么单纯了
The competition gets greedy.
他把所有人逼得太紧了
He starts pushing things too much.
当然 这要多多感谢我们潜伏着的自爆者们
With the help of my combustible double agent.
在一番使人警醒的对话后
And then after an arousing speech.
他最大的弱点显露了出来
His true weakness is revealed.
他爱上了 人类
He's in love…with humanity.
现在
And now.
我无人可挡
I'm inevitable.
那Josiah呢
What about Josiah.
他可能靠不住
He was a lose end.
我告诉他传送门的位置了
I told him where the gate was.
至少在我们转移地点之前
Before we moved it.
真希望Cass能不小心踩进我设下的陷阱
I just wish that Cass has walked in one of those traps.
不论如何 重点是
Anyway, the point is.
当其他人都醉心于西洋棋的时候
While everyone else is playing checkers.
我在玩儿大富翁
I'm playing monopoly.
而且我总能在大西洋城建旅馆
And I always build up a hotel on board walk.
赢家只能是我
And I always win.
所以 Dean
So, Dean.
我们到底要不要谈一谈
We're gonna talk about this or what.
谈什么
About what.
是啊 我撒谎了
Yeah, I lied.
但是你一直表现得像巨婴一样
But you're being an infant.
就算是你 这么道歉也很糟糕
Even for you, that apology sucks.
我这不是道歉
I'm not apologizing.
我只是在告诉你实情
I'm telling you how it's gonna be.
Dean
Dean.
初刃是唯一能杀死Metatron的东西
The Blade is the only thing that can kill Metatron.
而我是唯一可以使用初刃的人
And I'm the only one who can use it.
从现在开始 有我说了算 明白
So from here on, I'm calling the shots, capish.
在我一刀捅进那个混蛋的心脏之前
Until I jam that Blade to that douchbag's heart.
我们不是一队的
We're not a team.
这事儿我一人说了算
And this is a dictatorship.
我不需要听你的意见
And you don't have to like it.
事实就是这样
But that's how it's gonna be.
你怎么样
So, batteries.
- 我很好 - 不 你一点儿都不好
- I'm fine - No, you're not.
你的荣光还能坚持多长时间
How long do you get.
足够毁掉Metatron了 我希望
Long enough to destroy Metatron, I hope.
但我没有军队了
Not without an army.
你还有我们
You still got us.
Dean
Dean.
那些自爆者
Those bombers.
你不会真的以为是我
You don't really think that I.
你刚刚为了我放弃了整个军队
Guess you just gave up an entire army for one guy.
不可能是你 你不会叫那些人去送死的
No, there's no way that you blow those people away.
你真的相信仅凭我们三人就能成功
You really believe we three will be enough.
事情不向来如此吗
It always have been.
大家
Guys.
我不是来打架的
I'm not here to fight.
我仔细想了想你说的话
I thought about what you said.
你是对的
You're right.
Metatron他
Metatron he's.
有些事必须有人来做
Something needs to be done.
我们为什么要相信你
And we should trust you why.
因为我能把他交给你们
Because I can give him to you.
我知道Metatron在哪儿
I know where Metatron is.
我知道一切
I know everything.
我知道那些自爆者
I know the bombers, they.
他们是他的手下 不是你的
They were his agents, not yours.
你们不信任我 这我可以理解
You don't trust me, fine, I understand.
我 我犯过错
I've…made mistakes.
但难道你没有吗
But haven't you.
我们都没有错吗
Haven't we all.
至少给我一个机会
At least give me a chance.